//How well do you know the Julio-Claudian Emperors?
const questions = [
    {
    question: "Who among the Julio-Claudian emperors reigned the longest?",
    options: ["Augustus", "Tiberius", "Claudius", "Nero"],
    correctAnswer: "Augustus" 
    },
    {
    question: "What was Caligula's real name?",
    options: ["Marcus", "Titus", "Publius", "Gaius"],
    correctAnswer: "Gaius" 
    },
    {
    question: "Which emperor completed the conquest of Britain?",
    options: ["Tiberius", "Nero", "Claudius", "Caligula"],
    correctAnswer: "Claudius" 
    },
    {
    question: "Which of the emperors below was descended from both the Julian and Claudian families?",
    options: ["Augustus", "Claudius", "Tiberius", "Caligula"],
    correctAnswer: "Caligula" 
    },
    {
    question: "Who retired early to Rhodes, only to come out of retirement after just seven years?",
    options: ["Augustus", "Tiberius", "Claudius", "Nero"],
    correctAnswer: "Tiberius" 
    },
    {
    question: "Which emperor competed in the Olympic games?",
    options: ["Caligula", "Augustus", "Nero", "Claudius"],
    correctAnswer: "Nero" 
    },
    {
    question: "Which emperor invented and added letters to the Latin alphabet?",
    options: ["Claudius", "Augustus", "Caligula", "Tiberius"],
    correctAnswer: "Claudius" 
    },
    {
    question: "Which emperor conspired to have his own mother killed?",
    options: ["Caligula", "Claudius", "Tiberius", "Nero"],
    correctAnswer: "Nero" 
    },
    {
    question: "Who added Egypt to the Roman empire?",
    options: ["Tiberius", "Augustus", "Caligula", "Nero"],
    correctAnswer: "Augustus" 
    },
    {
    question: "Which of the Julio-Claudian emperors was the oldest when he died?",
    options: ["Tiberius", "Augustus", "Claudius", "Nero"],
    correctAnswer: "Tiberius" 
    }
];

